ERIKA POGORELC

+386 41 645256 → erika@serox.si → ercchy.github.com

PROFILE

Driven professional with broad technical skills which include design and development of web applications and a good knowledge of implementing backend solutions. I think of myself as highly resourceful, innovative, and competent software engineer. Strengths include:

- Python / Django / JavaScript
- Full cycle software development
- Driven to solve problems

- Web development, responsive design
- Excellent communication skills
- Great ability to multitask

I have a passion for software development and would like to further myself in software development, user experience design (UX), agile practices and teams. I invest heavily into my knowledge outside of regular work and it is not unusual of me to take a UX/HCI course at Coursera or attend a conference like EuroPython.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Python, Javascript, PHP, Java, C#

Frameworks: Django, JavaScriptMVC, CanJS, jQuery, Wordpress, Joomla

Methodologies: OOP, TDD, Agile development

Version control: git, github, bitbucket, subversion

Web development: HTML5, CSS3, responsive design, OOCSS, SASS, LESS,

Bootstrap, UX design, Gimp, Adobe Fireworks

Tools (IDE): PyCharm, Eclipse, Sublime Text 2

Operating systems: Linux (ubuntu, Amazon Linux), Windows

Databases: MySQL, AWS RDS MySQL, Toad for MySQL

Other: Amazon Web Services (AWS): console, AMIs, EC2, SES and

use of boto python library for AWS,

automated deployment: fabric and ansible and continuous

integration with Travis-CI

Familiar with concepts like PaaS, SaaS, laaS and different

cloud vendors

Knowledge of telecom domain: sales processes, ordering and

fulfillment, monthly billing and customer support

Volunteering at a local coding events and clubs as a mentor

ERIKA POGORELC

+386 41 645256 → erika@serox.si → ercchy.github.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Peer 2 Peer University, San Francisco, USA (telecommute)
Software engineer (March 2013 - present)

Developed software to offer more qualitative support for learners and facilitators of courses.

- Designed and implemented online assessment system to complement offered open courses,
- Usability testing and research about new open source services,
- Wordpress theme development for partners

Technologies used: Python, Django, Javascript, Amazon Web Services EC2, South, Ansible, SASS, Travis-CI, Twitter Bootstrap, Wordpress.

Petra Marketing d.o.o., Ljubljana / Si.Mobil d.d. Ljubljana, Slovenia Software engineer (February 2011 - March 2013)

Developed solutions to support cloud services platform offered by second largest telecom company in Slovenia (Si.Mobil).

- Designed and implemented marketplace web application that enables end-customers to order cloud services and get support,
- Designed, developed and implemented a web application to support sales processes.
 It includes functionality to manage accounts, lookup product price lists, product documentation, creation of quotes, required documentation generation in PDF, analytics and reporting,
- Provided support to telecom and their end-customers on how to use cloud applications and services (in-person or remote).

Technologies used: Python, Django, Amazon Web Services EC2, SES, boto, South, Fabric, django-compressor, janrain social login, crispy forms, HTML5 boilerplate, Twitter Bootstrap, LESS, Google Apps, Google Charts, various cloud vendors.

Redox d.o.o., Portorose, Slovenia

Application support engineer (September 2008 - January 2011)

Developed features and provided support for radio broadcasting digital audio solution and marinas prepaid system.

- Development of a server application of prepaid system for marinas. Application enabled visitors to marinas to use their amenities simply with a prepaid card,
- Designed and implemented a component for CMS system to enable radio stations to get access to schedules and forward them to their listeners,

ERIKA POGORELC

+386 41 645256 ◆ erika@serox.si ◆ ercchy.github.com

Technologies used: Java, sockets, PHP, Joomla, MySQL, CVS.

Prior to September 2008

I gained work experience working in non-IT related fields like charity organisation and sales department. More information available upon request.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. Software Engineering

Faculty of Computer and Information Science, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

REFERENCES

Available upon request.